logix.in 2019-02-22

# Logix InfoSecurity Pvt. Ltd. – Privacy Policy

**Logix Infosecurity Pvt. Ltd. Privacy Policy**

We recognize and respect your right to privacy. This policy explains how Logix Infosecurity Pvt Ltd (hereinafter “Logix”, “we” or “us”) collects and handles data. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your data and how we will treat it.

This Privacy Policy covers the following areas relating to privacy of information provided by you **:**

  * INTERPRETATION
  * LAWFUL BASIS OF PROCESSING
  * SHOULD YOU WANT TO OPT OUT
  * PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US
  * PURPOSE OF COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION BY US
  * CONSENT
  * MINORS
  * OTHER INFORMATION
  * CONTROL OVER YOUR INFORMATION
  * SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES AND WITHIN LOGIX
  * USE OF COOKIES
  * LINKS TO OTHER SITES
  * HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION
  * RETENTION AND DISPOSAL OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
  * CHANGES IN THIS POLICY
  * DATA PRIVACY ISSUES AND WHOM TO CONTACT

**INTERPRETATION**

For the purposes of this policy, the terms **personal information** and **sensitive personal information** shall mean the same as **personal data** and **special categories of personal data** , respectively. Other terms and their cognate terms shall carry the same meaning as they carry in GDPR or other applicable laws.

**LAWFUL BASIS OF PROCESSING**

We may process your information because:

  * We have a contract with you
  * You would have given us express permission to do so
  * We must have provided services to you after you have purchased something from us
  * We must have provided services to you because you have taken one of our offers
  * To comply with the law.

**SHOULD YOU WANT TO OPT OUT**

If we possess your contact information, we may want to keep you posted about our products, services and events, through email. Should you prefer not to keep up to date with Logix news and latest information on services and receive such marketing materials, please send an email to [unsubscribe@logix.in.](mailto:unsubscribe@logix.in.)

Further, you may withdraw the consent given to us on the website by communicating the same to us in writing. However, such withholding of information or withdrawal of consent may result in us not being able to provide services and facilities and we reserves its right to take appropriate action with respect to any obligations or in relation to any contract under which such personal information was sought.

We will update your preferences as soon as reasonably practical. However, do note, if you opt out of our emailing list, as described here, we may not be able to remove your personal information from all databases of Logix or other 3rd parties. For that, you would need to raise a request to erase your data as mentioned hereinafter.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US**

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may be gathered by us to serve you better. You may use most of our websites without supplying any personal information. However, our websites or certain parts of a site are available only if you obtain a password. We collect personal information when you register for a password, and at various other places on our site where you may register for a webinar/seminar or obtain or request other information or services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We also collect your personal information whenever you raise a query about our products or services, or anything else on our websites. This information includes collect your Company’s name, your name, Email ID and Mobile number

In addition, we automatically log the domain name of where you come from, the IP address your computer is currently using, the type of web browser that you use, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. This information allows us to improve the site by serving the pages you visit, and we may use the information for statistical purposes and to track usage patterns. In addition, we use the data we collect to make various determinations in our systems. We do not use this information to personally identify you, the user.

**PURPOSE OF COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION BY US**

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us and we take it very seriously. We will use your personal information to improve our offerings and your experience on our website, to provide you with the information, products or services you request from us or which we feel may interest you, to provide Support related to products and services you have purchased, to be able to identify you later when you contact us regarding products and services you have received from us, to provide you with information about and register you for webinars/seminars, to assign a password, to ensure that content from our website and services are presented in the most efficient manner for you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes, to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, to notify you about changes to our products or services, or to take other actions you request when you supply the Information.

**CONSENT**

Consent is often referred to as an individual’s choice to “opt-in” or “opt-out” the use of their personal information and is usually obtained by a “check box” or signature confirming the individual understands and agrees to the processing of their personal information. At times, express written consent from you may be required based on the information processing activity. Whenever required, we take consent from you prior to:

  * collecting, using, or processing your personal information, including sensitive personal data, in certain ways or sharing the your personal information with any third party (sensitive personal data is data revealing an your racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, genetic data, biometric data, data concerning health or data concerning sex life or sexual orientation);
  * transferring your personal information outside of your country of residence;
  * using or placing web cookies on your computer or other electronic devices.

**MINORS**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 18 years of age. As a parent or legal guardian, please do not to allow your children to submit personal information without your permission.

**OTHER INFORMATION**

We do not knowingly collect information related to your racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or other beliefs, health, criminal background or political affiliations, unless it is volunteered by you.

**CONTROL OVER YOUR INFORMATION**

We also provide you with the right to control your personal information, which includes the right to access, modify, erase, restrict, transmit, or object to certain uses of your information

You may request to review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise modify any of your Personal information that you have previously provided to us, or object to the use or processing of such Personal information by us. You have the ability to update your profile and related Personal information at any time. Also, you may review, update, correct or delete your Personal information collected through the website or service by e-mailing us at privacy@logix.in.

If you have privacy concerns regarding access to or the correction of your Personal information, please contact us at the contact information mentioned within the section called _“Data Privacy Issues and Whom to Contact”_ of this policy.

In your request, please make clear what Personal information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your Personal information that you have provided to us suppressed from our database or otherwise let us know what limitations you would like to put on our use of your Personal information that you have provided to us.

While the majority of questions and issues related to access or requests can be handled quickly, complex requests may take more research and time. In such cases, issues will be addressed, or you will be contacted regarding the nature of the problem and appropriate next steps, within 30 days.

**SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES AND WITHIN LOGIX**

We do not sell, hire, lease or rent the personal information we collect to anyone at this time. Unless we have your consent, are required by law, are required to do so in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements with you or are required to do so to protect our rights, property or safety, our customers or others, we will only provide personal information to third parties (Vendors) who assist us in operating our websites, resell our products or services, or help us with some products or services we provide. Data provided to third parties is stored on systems we do not own and is provided in accordance with our policies.

In the event of a merger, consolidation, sale, liquidation or transfer of assets, we may, in our sole and absolute discretion, transfer, sell or assign information collected, including without limitation, non-personal information and personal information, to one or more affiliated or unaffiliated third parties.

Also, we may, with or without prior notice to you, have to share your information in order to comply with applicable laws or respond to governmental inquiries or requests from public authorities or to comply with valid legal process, to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of Logix, its customers, employees or the public or to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain or to respond to an emergency.

**USE OF COOKIES**

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit our websites. This may include using cookies or similar technologies to identify your browser or device so that you do not have to re-enter your data upon each visit. Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer or mobile device that you are using. They allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the online services, pages visited, referring URL, language preferences, and other aggregated traffic data. Cookies and other technologies are also used to monitor usage of the various features and services of our site, which over time gives us information to improve our site, and to advertise and market our products more effectively. Cookies further allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on the online services or to send you advertisements and marketing emails. We may also use cookies or other technologies to track responses to our online advertisements and marketing emails.

When you visit our websites, cookies will be placed on your computer or device, to maximize your experience and to help us understand how we can improve our site. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can configure your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before a cookie is placed. If you disable cookies, some parts of our websites may not function properly or at all.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Our site contains links to third party websites. Please note that we will not be responsible for the collection, use, maintenance, sharing, or disclosure of data and information by such third parties. For information provided by you on third party sites, the privacy policy and terms of service on those sites will be applicable and we strongly advise you to read the privacy policies of websites that you visit before submitting personal information. If you choose to visit any of those sites then their privacy policies would apply. The Logix Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected from the Logix web site. We will not be responsible or liable for policies on third party websites. We have no control over the use of this technologies used by third parties on their websites, and will not be responsible or liable for any actions or policies of such third parties.

**HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION**

We are committed to taking steps to protect the Information you provide to us. For this, we take, and require any third party to take, reasonable precautions, including administrative, technical, and physical measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Access to your personal information is restricted to prevent unauthorised access, modification or misuse and such access is only granted to our employees and agents on a need-to-know basis. Your personal information is accessed only by authorized staff who are instructed to handle it with confidentiality. It is protected by firewalls and industry standard security measures. We may also transmit sensitive information and transactional data using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption.

However, unfortunately, no security system or system of transmitting data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be entirely secure. Once we have received Information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website site or our products and services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

**RETENTION AND DISPOSAL OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Your personal data will be retained in a form which enables us to identify you for no longer than it is necessary for the purposes for which the data was collected and used. Your personal data may be retained in certain files for a period of time as required by applicable law and following our data retention policies in order to comply with such financial or legal requirements, to properly resolve disputes or to troubleshoot problems. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us via the information stated hereinafter. We will respond to your request to access or delete your information within 30 days.

In addition, some types of information may be stored for an infinite duration due to technical constraints, and will be blocked from further processing for purposes which are not mandatory by law or when a consent is withdrawn. The information that you provide may be stored or transferred in our systems or on the systems provided by our third parties.

**CHANGES IN THIS POLICY**

We may update our privacy policy from time to time, without prior notice, and post it on the website. We recommend that you regularly visit this page to learn of any changes.

**DATA PRIVACY ISSUES AND WHOM TO CONTACT**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Global Privacy Policy or about how we handle your personal information, please get in touch with our Data Protection Officer (DPO) at [dpo@logix.in](mailto:dpo@logix.in). Alternatively, you may also contact us by clicking the  **Contact Us**  link on the website and following the appropriate links thereon.

You have the right to tell us if you:

  * do not wish to be contacted by us henceforth
  * would like to withdraw consent to personal data processing
  * wish to obtain a copy of your personal information that we hold
  * would like us to correct, update or delete your personal information in our records
  * wish to report any misuse of your personal information

To assist us in handling your request, please provide your full name and details. If you have any questions regarding this policy or our use of personally identifiable information on this site, please send us your questions or comments to [dpo@logix.in](mailto:dpo@logix.in).

Last Updated: Aug 08, 2018
